<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Evergrow Law</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Evergrow Law</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jeane Zhang</title>
      <link>/team/founder1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/founder1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Attorney Jeane Zhang brings over 20 years of legal experience advising corporations, startups, and entrepreneurs on complex legal matters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Known for her collaborative approach with executive and engineering teams, she supports clients throughout the product lifecycle—from concept to commercialization. Jeane has extensive experience developing robust IP portfolios and global patent strategies, helping companies across Silicon Valley and China navigate high-stakes legal challenges. A frequent speaker on intellectual property topics, her expertise spans patents, trademarks, copyrights, portfolio management, legal strategy, export control, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 1</title>
      <link>/services/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Financial accounting (or financial accountancy) is the field of accounting concerned with the &lt;strong&gt;summary, analysis and reporting&lt;/strong&gt; of financial transactions related to a business.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 2</title>
      <link>/services/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/service2/</guid>
      <description>Business Advisory is a specialized account service that offers expert guidance and strategic support to businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 3</title>
      <link>/services/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Business Sales refers to the process of selling a company or its assets to interested buyers, often involving the transfer of ownership and control.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 4</title>
      <link>/services/servers4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/servers4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mergers involve the combination of two or more companies into a single entity, typically aimed at achieving synergies, expanding market presence, or enhancing competitive advantages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 5</title>
      <link>/services/service5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/service5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We provide expert guidance on setting up and structuring superannuation funds, ensuring compliance with regulatory requirements, and implementing tax-efficient strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service 6</title>
      <link>/services/service6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/service6/</guid>
      <description>Our tax preparation accounting service offers a reliable and efficient solution for individuals and businesses seeking expert assistance in managing their tax obligations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EVERGROW Law LLP is a boutique corporate and intellectual property law firm dedicated to serving innovative startups and entrepreneurs. We provide specialized legal services across corporate transactions, regulatory compliance, and all aspects of intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With deep business insight and legal expertise, our team delivers strategic, cost-effective solutions to support clients through every stage of growth—from early formation to global expansion. Our goal is to empower visionary businesses with practical legal guidance that drives long-term success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have questions about patent protection, enforcement, or other intellectual property matters? Our team at Evergrow Law is ready to assist you. Please use the information below to get in touch, and we&amp;rsquo;ll respond promptly to your inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Email:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tel:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Day&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Opening Hours&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Monday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;9:00am - 5:00pm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Tuesday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;9:00am - 5:00pm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Wednesday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;9:00am - 5:00pm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Thursday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;9:00am - 5:00pm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Friday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;9:00am - 5:00pm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Saturday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Closed&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Sunday&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Closed&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
